iiserpune.ac.in 2018-12-20

# IISER Pune

Privacy Policy 

**Site Visit Data**

IISER Pune gathers certain information about the users, such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, domain name, browser type, operating system, the date and time of visit to the IISER Pune website and the pages visited. No attempt is made to link these addresses with the identity of individuals visiting IISER Pune site unless an attempt to damage the site has been detected. With this data, we learn about the number of visitors to IISER Pune site and the types of technology these visitors use, which helps us improve our website. IISER Pune never tracks or records information about individuals and their visits.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of software code that an internet website sends to your browser when you access information at that site. IISER Pune website may also use cookies.

**Email Management**

Your email address will only be recorded if you choose to send a message. It will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it and will not be added to a mailing list. Your email address will not be used for any other purpose, and will not be disclosed, without your consent.

**Collection of Personal Information**

If you are asked for any other Personal Information you will be informed how it will be used if you choose to give it. If at any time you believe the principles referred to in this privacy statement have not been followed, or have any other comments on these principles, please notify the webmaster through the contact us page.

Note: The use of the term "Personal Information" in this privacy statement refers to any information. from which your identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained.
